<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/sk/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
	<string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Petr &lt; svobodnik.petr@gmail.com &gt;" orig="WebSMS lets you send free and very cheap TXT/SMS via different webservices.\n\nYou will need at least one WebSMS Connector (plugin/extension) from the market to connect this app to the webservice of your choice.\nPricing depends on the webservice provider connected with the connector.\nThe Connector shipped with the app itself sends messages via standard GSM method and is billed by your operator. It is installed for backup reasons and deactivated by default.">WebSMS umožňuje bezplatně a velmi levně odesílat textové SMS pomocí různých webových služeb.\n\nK tomu potřebujete alespoň jedno WebSMS rozhraní (plugin/rozšíření), které naleznete na marketu. Rozhraní umožňuje připojit WebSMS k webové službě, kterou si vyberete. \nCeny závisí na poskytovateli webové služby, na kterou rozhraní umožňuje připojení.\n\"SMS\" rozhraní, které je součástí WebSMS umožňuje odesílat zprávy přes GSM a každá zpráva je účtována Vaším operátorem. SMS rozhraní je ve výchozím stavu vypnuté a je dostupné pouze z důvodu podpory.</string>
	<string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Petr &lt; svobodnik.petr@gmail.com &gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Tato aplikace je vytvářena ve volném čase jako open source. Přidáním negativních komentářů na Google Play nevylepšíte její vývoj.\nPřípadné problémy ohlašujte na webových stránkách aplikace.</string>
	<string name="market_smsdroid" formatted="false" username="Petr &lt; svobodnik.petr@gmail.com &gt;" orig="As WebSMS is not able to read messages you might find SMSdroid useful.\nSMSdroid is an alternativ message reader for people who are sending messages with any other messaging app like WebSMS.">WebSMS neumožňuje čtení Vašich zpráv. K tomuto účelu slouží aplikace SMSdroid.\nSMSdroid je alternativa pro čtení zpráv, které odesíláte z jiných aplikací k tomu určených, např. WebSMS.</string>
	<string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Petr &lt; svobodnik.petr@gmail.com &gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/">Pomozte přeložit tuto aplikaci do Vašeho rodného jazyka, informace zde: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/</string>
</resources>
