<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/ru/help.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="help_title" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Introducing WebSMS">Представляем WebSMS</string>
  <string name="get_connectors" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Get Connectors">Получить Коннекторы</string>
  <string name="help_conenctors" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="There is a huge number of Connectors available in Google Play Store.\nPress the button below and install the Connector which suits you best.\nFor users without an account at any of the service, I recommend cherry-sms for almost everybody. Users with non latin alphabets might want to try my-cool-sms first.">В Google Play доступно огромное количество Коннекторов.\nНажмите на кнопку ниже и установите Коннектор, который подходит вам лучше всего.\nДля пользователей, не имеющих счета в какой-либо службе, я рекомендую cherry-sms. Пользователям с не латинскими алфавитами в первую очередь стоит попробовать my-cool-sms.</string>
  <string name="help_connectors_matrix" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="You might want to check the Connector Matrix for more informations about avaiable Connectors: http://code.google.com/p/websmsdroid/wiki/ConnectorMatrix">Посмотрите Connector Matrix для получения более подробной информации о доступных Коннекторах: http://code.google.com/p/websmsdroid/wiki/ConnectorMatrix</string>
  <string name="help_prefs" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="To get started, you need at least set your own mobile number and international prefix in WebSMS\'s preferences.">Для начала, Вам необходимо, как минимум, указать собственный номер мобильного телефона и международный префикс в настройках WebSMS.</string>
  <string name="help_html_title" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Help - %s">Справка - %s</string>
  <string name="rules_editor_help" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&#10;&lt;p&gt;Here you can define connector selection rules.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Click \&quot;+\&quot; to add a rule&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Click a rule to view or modify it&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Long-click a rule to delete or move it&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Return to the previous screen to save the changes&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Click Cancel to forget all changes&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Each rule defines which connector should be used if a message matches the given conditions. For example,&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;if the recipient\'s number starts with +1323 then use connector X&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;if the recipient\'s number starts with +1 then use connector Y&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;if none of the above then use connector Z&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Rules are evaluated in the displayed order and when the &lt;b&gt;first&lt;/b&gt;&#10;matching rule is found, its target connector is used for sending the message.&#10;The remaining rules are ignored. In the above example, a message to +1323777 will be sent&#10;using connector X and a message to +1505888 will be sent using connector Y.&#10;It is recommended to add \&quot;if none of the above\&quot; as the last rule,&#10;which will define the default connector for all remaining recipients.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If you want to verify that your rules work correctly, you can tick \&quot;Test only\&quot;&#10;in Preferences and try sending messages to different recipients.&#10;In this mode, the chosen connector will be shown but no messages will actually be sent.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;    ">&lt;p&gt;Здесь вы можете определить правила выбора коннектора.&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Нажмите "+" для добавления правила&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Просмотреть или изменить правило - нажмите на него&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Удаление или перемещение правила - длинное нажатие на него&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Сохранить изменения - вернитесь на предыдущий экран&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Забыть все изменения - нажмите Отмена&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Каждое правило определяет, какой коннектор следует использовать, если сообщение соответствует заданным условиям. Например,&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;если номер получателя начинается с +1323, использовать коннектор X&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;если номер получателя начинается с +1, использовать коннектор Y&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;если не удовлетворяет ни одному из вышеперечисленных условий, использовать коннектор Z&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Правила применяются в порядке их следования в программе и когда <b>первое</b>\nподходящее правило найдено, выбранный коннектор используется для отправки сообщения. \nОстальные правила игнорируются. В приведенном выше примере, сообщение +1323777 будет отправлено с помощью коннектора X, сообщение +1505888 будет отправлено с помощью коннектора Y.\nРекомендуется добавить "если не удовлетворяет ни одному из вышеперечисленных условий", как последнее правило, которое будет определять коннектор по умолчанию для всех остальных получателей.&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Если вы хотите убедиться, что ваши правила работают правильно, установите галочку "Только тест"\nв Настройках и попробуйте отправить сообщения различным получателям.\nВ этом режиме, будет показан выбранный коннектор, но ни одно сообщение не будет на самом деле отправлено.&lt;/p&gt;\n</string>
  <string name="edit_rule_help" formatted="false" username="Dmitriy Rublev &lt;kaktebyavirubit@gmail.com&gt;" orig="&#10;&lt;p&gt;Here you can view or modify details of a rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The first section defines which recipient numbers this rule shall apply to:&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;ul&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;starts with - the rule applies if the recipient\'s number starts with the given prefix&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;Regular Expression - the rule applies if the recipient\'s number matches the Regular Expression&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;li&gt;any number - the rule always applies (this is normally used for the last \&quot;none of the above\&quot; rule)&lt;/li&gt;&#10;&lt;/ul&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The last section defines which connector shall be used in this case.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Optionally, you can limit the character set that this provider can accept.&#10;Some providers do not support non-English (e.g. Cyrillic) characters.&#10;In this case, you can click \&quot;English (Latin) characters only\&quot;, which means that this connector&#10;will only be used if your message only contains digits, letters \&quot;a-Z\&quot; and basic punctuation (ASCII set).&#10;Otherwise (or if you don\'t know what this all means), leave it at default \&quot;any characters\&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To save the rule, return to the previous screen.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To forget all changes, click Cancel.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;    ">&lt;p&gt;Здесь Вы можете просмотреть или изменить информацию о правиле.&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Первый раздел определяет, на какие номера получателей это правило распространяется:&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;ul&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;начинается с - правило применяется, если номер получателя начинается с заданного префикса&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;Регулярное выражение - правило применяется, если номер получателя совпадает с регулярным выражением&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;li&gt;любой номер - правило применяется всегда (это, как правило, используется в случае правила "если не удовлетворяет ни одному из вышеперечисленных условий")&lt;/li&gt;\n&lt;/ul&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;В последнем разделе определяется коннектор, использующийся в конкретном случае.&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;При желании, вы можете ограничить набор символов, принимаемых провайдером.\nНекоторые провайдеры не поддерживают отличные от английских (например, кириллические) символы.\nВ этом случае, вы можете нажать кнопку "Только английские (латиница) символы", что означает, что коннектор будет использоваться только в том случае, если сообщение содержит только цифры, буквы "AZ" и основную пунктуацию (ASCII набор).\nВ противном случае (или если вы не понимаете, что это значит), оставьте значение по умолчанию - "любые символы".&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Сохранить изменения - вернитесь на предыдущий экран.&lt;/p&gt;\n&lt;p&gt;Забыть все изменения - нажмите Отмена.&lt;/p&gt;\n</string>
</resources>
