<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/sk/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Ing. Štefan Tokár &lt;matelkoxxl@gmail.com&gt;" orig="WebSMS lets you send free and very cheap TXT/SMS via different webservices.\n\nYou will need at least one WebSMS Connector (plugin/extension) from the market to connect this app to the webservice of your choice.\nPricing depends on the webservice provider connected with the connector.\nThe &quot;SMS&quot; Connector shipped with the app itself sends messages via standard GSM method and is billed by your operator. It is installed for backup reasons and deactivated by default.">WebSMS ti umožní posielať TXT/SMS správy lacno, alebo dokonca zadarmo cez rôzne webové služby.\n\nPotrebujete k tomu minimálne jeden WebSMS Connector (plugin/rozšírenie) z Google Play na prepojenie tejto aplikácie s webovou službou, ktorú ste si vybrali.\nCena závisí na poskytovateľovi prepojenej webovej služby.\n"SMS" Connector dodaný s aplikáciou posiela správy cez Vášho operátora a je ním aj účtovaný. Ja nainštalovaný zo záložných dôvodov a štandartne je deaktivovaný.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Ing. Štefan Tokár &lt;matelkoxxl@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Táto aplikácia je programovaná vo voľnom čase ako open source. Pridávanie negatívnych komentárov v Google Play nepomáha robiť ju lepšou.\nProsím všetky Vaše návrhy a chyby pridávajte priamo na Web stránku autora.</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Ing. Štefan Tokár &lt;matelkoxxl@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/">Neváhajte pomôcť s prekladom tejto aplikácie do Vášho jazyka tu:</string>
  <string name="market_smsdroid" formatted="false" username="Ing. Štefan Tokár &lt;matelkoxxl@gmail.com&gt;" orig="As WebSMS is not able to read messages you might find SMSdroid useful.\nSMSdroid is an alternativ message reader for people who are sending messages with any other messaging app like WebSMS.">WebSMS neumožňuje čítanie Vašich správ. K tomuto účelu slúži aplikácia SMSdroid.\nSMSdroid je alternatíva pre čítanie správ, ktoré odosielate z iných aplikácií k tomu určených, napr. WebSMS.</string>
</resources>
