<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
	<!--
		Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
	-->
	<!--
		This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
		redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
		Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
		version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
	-->
	<!--
		This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
		WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
		MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
		General Public License for more details. You should have received a
		copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
		not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
	-->
<resources>
	<string name="help_title">Introducing WebSMS</string>
	<string name="get_connectors">Get Connectors</string>
	<string name="help_conenctors">There is a huge number of Connectors available in Google Play Store.\nPress the button below and install the Connector which suits you best.\nFor users without an account at any of the service, I recommend cherry-sms for almost everybody. Users with non latin alphabets might want to try my-cool-sms first.</string>
	<string name="help_connectors_matrix">You might want to check the Connector Matrix for more informations about avaiable Connectors: https://github.com/felixb/websms/blob/master/ConnectorMatrix.md</string>
	<string name="help_prefs">To get started, you need at least set your own mobile number and international prefix in WebSMS\'s preferences.</string>

    <string name="help_html_title">Help - %s</string>
    <string name="rules_editor_help">
&lt;p&gt;Here you can define connector selection rules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click \"+\" to add a rule&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click a rule to view or modify it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long-click a rule to delete or move it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to the previous screen to save the changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click Cancel to forget all changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each rule defines which connector should be used if a message matches the given conditions. For example,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if the recipient\'s number starts with +1323 then use connector X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if the recipient\'s number starts with +1 then use connector Y&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;if none of the above then use connector Z&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rules are evaluated in the displayed order and when the &lt;b&gt;first&lt;/b&gt;
matching rule is found, its target connector is used for sending the message.
The remaining rules are ignored. In the above example, a message to +1323777 will be sent
using connector X and a message to +1505888 will be sent using connector Y.
It is recommended to add \"if none of the above\" as the last rule,
which will define the default connector for all remaining recipients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to verify that your rules work correctly, you can tick \"Test only\"
in Preferences and try sending messages to different recipients.
In this mode, the chosen connector will be shown but no messages will actually be sent.&lt;/p&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="edit_rule_help">
&lt;p&gt;Here you can view or modify details of a rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first section defines which recipient numbers this rule shall apply to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;starts with - the rule applies if the recipient\'s number starts with the given prefix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regular Expression - the rule applies if the recipient\'s number matches the Regular Expression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;any number - the rule always applies (this is normally used for the last \"none of the above\" rule)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last section defines which connector shall be used in this case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optionally, you can limit the character set that this provider can accept.
Some providers do not support non-English (e.g. Cyrillic) characters.
In this case, you can click \"English (Latin) characters only\", which means that this connector
will only be used if your message only contains digits, letters \"a-Z\" and basic punctuation (ASCII set).
Otherwise (or if you don\'t know what this all means), leave it at default \"any characters\".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To save the rule, return to the previous screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To forget all changes, click Cancel.&lt;/p&gt;
    </string>

</resources>
