<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/edit.php?lang=ru&file=market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="ergodroid &lt;ergodroid@gmail.com&gt;" orig="WebSMS let\'s you send free and very cheap TXT/SMS via different webservices.\n\nYou will need at least one WebSMS Connector (plugin/extension) from the market to connect this app to the webservice of your choice.\nPricing depends on the webservice provider connected with the connector.\nThe &quot;SMS&quot; Connector shipped with the app itself sends messages via standard GSM method and is billed by your operator. It is installed for backup reasons and deactivated by default.">WebSMS позволяет отправлять SMS бесплатно или по низкой цене через разные интернет сервисы по отправке SMS.\nВам понадобиться Коннектор (плагин/расширение) для WebSMS, чтобы подключиться и отправлять SMS через выбранный Вами сервис. Цены зависят от провайдера данных услуг и провайдера мобильного интернета. По умолчанию с программой поставляется коннектор, который отправляет SMS через сотового оператора. </string>
  <string name="market_smsdroid" formatted="false" username="" orig="As WebSMS is not able to read messages you might find SMSdroid useful.\nSMSdroid is an alternativ message reader for people who are sending messages with any other messaging app like WebSMS.">WebSMS не умеет принимать и читать сообщения, поэтому возможно SMSdroid будет Вам более полезен. SMSdroid - альтернативный ридер сообщений для тех, кто использует нестандартные приложения для отправки SMS, такие как WebSMS.</string>
  <string name="market_keywords" formatted="false" orig="Keywords: freesms sms txt websms messages">Keywords: freesms бесплатные смс websms сообщения u-sms smspilot</string>
</resources>
