<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/fr/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Christian Knecht &lt;g.chrisk@gmail.com&gt;" orig="WebSMS lets you send free and very cheap TXT/SMS via different webservices.\n\nYou will need at least one WebSMS Connector (plugin/extension) from the market to connect this app to the webservice of your choice.\nPricing depends on the webservice provider connected with the connector.\nThe &quot;SMS&quot; Connector shipped with the app itself sends messages via standard GSM method and is billed by your operator. It is installed for backup reasons and deactivated by default.">WebSMS vous permet d\'envoyer des SMS gratuitement ou à des tarifs intéressants via différents services web.\n\nIl vous faut au moins un connecteur (plugin/extension) WebSMS que vous trouverez sur le Play Store afin de connecter cette application au service web de votre choix.\nLes prix dépendent du fournisseur de service sur lequel le connecteur s\'appuie.\nLe connecteur nommé \"SMS\", qui est livré en standard avec l\'application WebSMS elle-même, envoie des SMS standards GSM par votre téléphone qui vous seront donc facturés par votre opérateur. Ce connecteur est installé dans l\'idée d\'une solution de secours et est désactivé par défaut.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Christian Knecht &lt;g.chrisk@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Cette application est open source et écrite pendant mon temps libre. Ajouter des commentaires négatifs sur Play Store n\'aidera pas beaucoup à la rendre meilleure. Signaler plutôt vos problèmes sur le site de l\'application.</string>
  <string name="market_smsdroid" formatted="false" username="Christian Knecht &lt;g.chrisk@gmail.com&gt;" orig="As WebSMS is not able to read messages you might find SMSdroid useful.\nSMSdroid is an alternativ message reader for people who are sending messages with any other messaging app like WebSMS.">WebSMS n\'étant pas en mesure de lire vos messages, vous pourriez trouver SMSdroid utile. SMSdroid est un lecteur de message alternatif pour les personnes qui envoient des messages avec des applications telles que WebSMS.</string>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Christian Knecht &lt;g.chrisk@gmail.com&gt;" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/">Sentez vous libre d\'aider à la traduction de cette application dans votre langue ici: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/</string>
</resources>
