<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
               Copyright (C) 2009-2011 Felix Bechstein
       -->
<!--
               This file is part of WebSMS. This program is free software; you can
               redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General
               Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation; either
               version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.
       -->
<!--
               This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but
               WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
               MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
               General Public License for more details. You should have received a
               copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program; If
               not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
       -->
<!--
               This file is generated automatically by ub0rlib/php.
               Visit http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/uk/market.xml to edit the file.
       -->
<resources>
  <string name="market_translation" formatted="false" username="Ukrainian" orig="Feel free to help translating this app to your language here: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms/">Ви можете допомогти перекласти цей застосунок на вашу мову тут: http://ub0r.de/translate/websms</string>
  <string name="market_smsdroid" formatted="false" username="Андрій Бандура  &lt;andriykopanytsya@gmail.com&gt;" orig="As WebSMS is not able to read messages you might find SMSdroid useful.\nSMSdroid is an alternativ message reader for people who are sending messages with any other messaging app like WebSMS.">Якщо WebSMS не взмозі прочитати ваші повідомлення, можливо вам слід встановити SMSdroid. SMSdroid це альтернативний читач смс\'ок для людей, які посилають повідомлення за допомокою інших програм смс на кшталт WebSMS.</string>
  <string name="market_oss" formatted="false" username="Андрій Бандура  &lt;andriykopanytsya@gmail.com&gt;" orig="This app is open source software build in spare time. Adding bad comments in market won\'t help much to make it better.\nPlease add your issues with this app on the app\'s website.">Ця програма є ПЗ з відкритим вихідним кодом, створеним у вільний час. Додавання негативний відгуків на Android Маркеті не особливо допоможе зробити її кращою.\nБудь ласка, замість злих коментарів, додавайте ваші проблеми з цієї програмою на її сайті.</string>
  <string name="market_about" formatted="false" username="Андрій Бандура  &lt;andriykopanytsya@gmail.com&gt;" orig="WebSMS lets you send free and very cheap TXT/SMS via different webservices.\n\nYou will need at least one WebSMS Connector (plugin/extension) from the market to connect this app to the webservice of your choice.\nPricing depends on the webservice provider connected with the connector.\nThe &quot;SMS&quot; Connector shipped with the app itself sends messages via standard GSM method and is billed by your operator. It is installed for backup reasons and deactivated by default.">WebSMS дозволяє безкоштовно і дуже дешево відправляти  TXT/SMS за допомогою веб-сервісів.\n\nВам буде необхідний хоча б один WebSMS Приєднувач (модуль/розширення) з маркету, аби підключити цю програму до вибраного вами веб-сервісу.\nЦіна залежить від веб-сервісу постачальника з\'єднаного з Приєднувачем.\nSMS Приєднувач, що входить до програми, сам відсилає повідомлення стандартним GSM методом і тарифікується вашим оператором. Він встановлюється на резервний випадок і є вимкнутим за замовчуванням.</string>
</resources>
